(Sheldon:)Good for me.
(Leonard:)Yeah, good for you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, wait.
Did you wanna talk about
what's bothering you?
- I don't know. Maybe.
- Wow, I'm on fire tonight.
Well, here's the thing.
(Leonard:)Girls like Penny never end up with guys
who own time machines.
(Sheldon:)I disagree.
(Sheldon:)Your inability
to successfully woo Penny...
(Sheldon:)...long predates your acquisition
of the time machine.
(Sheldon:)That failure clearly stands on its own.
- Thanks for pointing it out.
- In addition, your premise is flawed.
(Sheldon:)In the original film,
Rod Taylor got Yvette Mimieux...
...with that time machine.
(Sheldon:)In Back to the Future,
Marty McFly got to hook up...
(Sheldon:)...with his extremely attractive
young mother.
- Those are movies.
- Of course they're movies.